Contact

087889272637

syafanurwalinda23@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/fikriansyah-515512245

Skills

Javascript
Node js
TypeScript
Vue.js
React Js
Next Js
React Native

Languages

Bahasa Indonesia Bahasa Inggris



Fikri Ansyah

Full Stack Developer | Typescript, Vue, React.Js, Next.Js

Profile

Hi, I am a passionate software developer and IT enthusiast. I have 2 years experience in IT field, starting from majoring in computer network engineering vocation high school and majoring in Information Systems at Pamulang University. I am a positive person who loved to challenge my self and always willing to learn more. I am also reliable and have a strong sense of discipline.

As a software developer, I possess strong analytical skills to identify problems and find appropriate solutions. I am capable of working collaboratively in a team, communicating effectively, and being flexible in adapting to technological advancements and project requirements.

Pengalaman

BerandaToko
Frontend Developer
Desember 2022 - Present (8 bulan)
Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

- Build Frontend apps with Vuejs, Reactjs, Laravue
- Integration API payment gateway
- BERANDATOKO and JESSIE and Coster

Keahlian: Docker \cdot React.js \cdot PostgreSQL \cdot Vue.js \cdot PHP \cdot Laravel \cdot JavaScript REST APIs \cdot MySQL

- BERANDATOKO and JESSIE
- Collaborate with UI/UX and product manager to improve the user design and user experience
- Bug fixing and added new feature
- · Write technical requirement documents and guides
- Unit testing (jest or cypress) Collaborate with back-end developers to improve the usability

- Manual testing before begin given to QA• BERANDATOKO and JESSIE
- Collaborate with UI/UX and product manager to improve the user design and user experience
 Bug fixing and added new feature
 Write technical requirement documents and guides
 Unit testing (jest or cypress)
 Collaborate with back-end developers to improve the usability
 Manual testing

Keahlian: Laravue · Vue.js · Laravel · REST APIs

Jatis Mobile

Frontend Developer

before begin given to QA

Desember 2022 - Present (8 bulan)

Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

- Build Frontend apps with Vuejs, Reactjs, Laravue
- Integration API payment gateway
- BERANDATOKO and JESSIE and Coster

Keahlian: Docker · React.js · PostgreSQL · Vue.js · PHP · Laravel · JavaScript

- · REST APIs · MySQL
- BERANDATOKO and JESSIE
- Collaborate with UI/UX and product manager to improve the user design and user experience
- Bug fixing and added new feature
- Write technical requirement documents and guides
- Unit testing (jest or cypress)
- Collaborate with back-end developers to improve the usability
- Manual testing before begin given to QA
- BERANDATOKO and JESSIE
- Collaborate with UI/UX and product manager to improve the user design and user experience
- Bug fixing and added new feature
- Write technical requirement documents and guides
- Unit testing (jest or cypress)
- Collaborate with back-end developers to improve the usability
- Manual testing before begin given to QA

Keahlian: Laravue · Vue.js · Laravel · REST APIs

Sagara Technology
Back End Developer
November 2022 - Februari 2023 (4 bulan)

Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

Pendidikan

Universitas Pamulang

Gelar Sarjana, Teknik Informatika · (Januari 2019 - Desember 2023)

PT. DumbWays Indonesia Teknologi

· (Mei 2022 - Agustus 2022)